The Magic Roundabout is a animation, family, comedy
film directed by Frank Passingham.
A shaggy, candy-loving puppy named Dougal along with a group of friends embarks on a dangerous journey in an
effort to imprison their oppressor -- the evil ice sorcerer ZeeBad (Zebedee's evil twin).
As the world is placed in mortal danger Zeebad who
wants to turn the world to ice.
Doogal and his friends must recover 3 diamonds that are needed to stop him.
Dougal (voice), played by Robbie Williams.
Florence (voice), played by Kylie Minogue.
Zebedee (voice), played by Ian McKellen.
Ermintrude (voice), played by Joanna Lumley.
Brian (voice), played by Jim Broadbent.
Dylan (voice), played by Bill Nighy.
The Magic Roundabout (also known as Sprung!
The Magic Roundabout; French: Pollux – Le manège enchanté) is a 2005 animated adventure
fantasy comedy film based on the television series  of the same name.
Unlike the show, which was presented with stop-motion animation,
the film utilizes computer-generated animation.
The story sees a group of unlikely heroes who go on a quest to stop a reawakened villain, who
intends on freezing the world, from retrieving a set of powerful diamonds.
It was released in France with an original French dub on 2 February 2005, and an
English-language version was released nine days later in the United Kingdom on 11 February.
In the United States, the film was released as Doogal on 24
February 2006 with a new English cast, dub, and script.
Only Ian McKellen's performance was retained, while Kylie
Minogue redubbed her role from the UK release.
Whilst the UK and French dub received mixed reviews, the US
dub received overwhelmingly negative reviews.
The tone is lighthearted.